The evil spirit in this man was among the many who could not escape the anointing of God.
There is a spiritual battle between the forces of light and the forces of darkness.
As Wise Man Daniel battles the spiritual entities causing crises in this man's life,
the evil spirits are in trouble and heading towards extinction.
Let us watch to see how the encounter between Wise Man Daniel and the evil spirit ended.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ! All over your body.
All over your body, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Your face, your legs - fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Anywhere you wicked demon are located -
fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Fire! All over your body, you demon!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Right now, speak out!
Allow me to go.
Who are you?
Do you want to know me?
Jesus wants to know you. Speak out!
Who are you?
Let me speak.
Speak! You have no choice; you must.
Who are you?
The spirit of lust.
How many of you are in this body?
Three.
Who is the second person?
Spiritual wife.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
The last person?
Spirit of anger.
Ok. As spirit of anger, how do you operate in this body?
I make him angry.
When he is angry, what happens in the house?
He fights and tries to beat the wife.
Does he slap or kick?
He slaps and kicks.
How do you feel each time he is slapping and kicking the wife?
How do you feel, you demon?
I feel good.
You feel good?
Yes, very good.
How has this spirit of anger affected the marriage?
Which marriage?
His marriage.
He doesn't have any marriage.
No marriage.
No marriage?
No.
We don't have anything to talk about marriage.
Ok. As spiritual wife, what have you done to his career as a man?
I destroyed everything.
This guy - do you know this guy?
You don't know him.
He is a very great guy.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I destroyed everything - nothing to write about.
What are the things he had that you have destroyed?
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Uncountable.
This man you see here was worth millions but I made him suffer
and lose every business he put his money into.
I destroyed those businesses.
What kind of business was he doing that you destroyed?
Importation, of course.
Ehe.
How did you destroy those things?
Whenever he imports it, one story or the other.
I am the one that did it.
Is it that you seize his containers or how do you go about it?
Yes, I seized it - a lot of them.
Like how many did you succeed in getting seized?
Millions worth of naira.
He is a great man. He is a rich man.
You don't know him. He had been abroad for many years.
For more than 13 years, he made money.
But I made sure I wiped all the money.
How do you operate in him as spirit of lust?
I seduce women.
How do you use him to go about that?
When they look at his eyes?
With my eyes, of course.
What happens? Explain.
They will lose control, of course.
When they lose control, what happens to them?
They will be following me everywhere.
How do you use your eyes to move them?
Can't you see it?
In my eyes.
Do you smile or you just stand there?
Charming - charming eyes.
That is how you do it?
Yes.
Those who are married among them, what happens to their marriage?
I don't have anything to do with married women.
Ok. Those who are not married, what happens to them?
They follow me everywhere.
When they follow you, what happens to them? Will they have a settled home?
No.
Ok. What happens to them that makes them not to have a settled home?
They will be roaming about.
They will not even see any man who will marry them.
How many have you succeeded in destroying like this?
Many; I can't count them.
You can't count them?
Yes.
Ok. Who is this woman to you?
Which woman?
I don't know.
What about this gentleman here?
I am alone.
How are you, ma?
I am fine, sir.
Who is he to you?
He is my husband.
Ok. What about you?
We are from the same place and we have been together in Switzerland for many years.
As a wife, what can you say about your husband?
He has the spirit of lust, as he said.
Even now, he has a girl who used to call and insult me.
She would tell me all sort of things, that my husband will marry her
and drive me out of the house.
His family accused me that I am the one who is scattering his business.
In the marriage, there is no peace.
They told him to throw me out of the house, that I am a witch
and the one scattering his family.
So, I decided to come here so that God would expose whoever was doing this.
Ok. Your in-laws always accuse you that you are the one causing trouble?
Yes, his family accused me that I was the one who was scattering his business,
that he should throw me out.
Even the business he opened for me, he seized it.
He beats me every day in the house. He has the spirit of anger
and he has the spirit of unforgiveness. He doesn't forgive easily.
So, you demon, it is time you vacate this body!
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body, you demon, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You have no choice.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus' name!
Thank You, Lord!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
You are free.
Rise up, you are free.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Come, sir.
How are you, sir?
I'm fine.
Stand up, sir.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Don't worry.
Who is this woman?
She is my wife.
Ok. What about the gentleman here?
He is my brother.
He is my lovely brother.
So, ma, listen. The reason why I asked him this question is for you to know that the past is over.
The confession you heard was not from your husband.
This is a different person.
The person who spoke was not your husband but a demon
and that demon is out.
So, for no reason should you remind him of what happened today
so that you will not be tempted, okay?
Okay. Thank You, Jesus for saving my family and marriage!
Give thanks to God. You are free.
Stand up, sir!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, God of T.B. Joshua, for saving my marriage and my home!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mr Okpalaeze Chidi.
I am originally from Enugu State
but I stayed in Switzerland for many years.
The woman beside me is my lovely wife, Stella Okpalaeze.
I am here to testify to the goodness of the Lord in my life.
What God has done in my life - I don't know how to state it.
My testimony goes like this.
I have been abroad for 14 to 15 years now.
I kept on having this problem of setback in business -
any business I was involved in kept on crumbling.
I was not moving forward the way I was supposed to
because I trust myself in anything I am doing.
I know I am capable to handle it.
It kept on happening.
Not until I came back to Nigeria.
I have been to many churches.
Ok, brother.
Before going ahead, you mentioned that, first of all, this problem manifested in the form of business collapsing.
But, apart from that, what experiences did you begin to have in your dreams
that made you realise that something was happening?
A woman used to visit me in my dreams.
Sometimes, when I woke up, I would see my clothes to be wet.
Many times when I would be sleeping with my wife,
she would wake me up and ask me, "What are you doing?
You are doing as if you are making love to somebody".
If she woke me up, I would continue to sleep again.
But it kept on happening to me every time.
I tried my best to hide it from everybody.
But every time I was sleeping, the woman would come in my dreams to make love to me.
Anytime this thing happened, any business I put my hand on - nothing would work out.
The business started to turn back.
I am into importation.
I have travelled to many countries.
I import containers but one problem or the other -
either they would seize it or the people I did the business with would dupe me.
I sponsored many things but at the end, none of them worked out.
I even tried to use my wife to go on with the business.
I invested millions of naira in the business I opened for her.
But at the end of it, nothing came out of it. The same thing happened.
I even realised that the thing was just like a virus.
Anybody I did something with, the same thing would happen.
I thought it was something I could handle myself.
I knew that something was wrong somewhere
but I could not exactly figure it out.
I thought I knew what to do.
The best friend I had was alcohol.
I drank in the morning, afternoon and night.
I didn't have a brand.
I involved myself in many things -
womanising, clubbing - just to try to make myself happy.
I didn't know that the way I was going was the wrong way.
I couldn't sleep.
I took all kinds of tablets to make me sleep but I couldn't sleep.
I would go to bed with acute headache,
and I would wake up with acute headache.
It got to a point where my mother even started asking me whether I was smoking Indian hemp
because my eyes were always red.
You know that when somebody would go to bed and would not sleep,
the same way you went to bed would be the same way you would wake up.
What would happen that you would find women easily being attracted to you?
You know that it is a man that is in the position to toast a woman
but there was something in me, in my eyes.
Wherever I came in or any woman I came across,
if I looked at her, she would be following me, going after me.
They didn't need my money. They just wanted me to sleep with them.
For example, I was at a junction one day, my car had broken down.
A girl looked at me and greeted me.
Immediately I drove out, the girl took a bike and went after me.
Not until I found myself at a joint where I sat down to drink something,
the girl came in, sat down and greeted me.
I now said to myself, "Is this not the same girl I saw at the junction?"
She began to toast me.
You can imagine where a woman would be proud to talk to a man,
that she wanted to be with you.
I noticed this thing many times.
It happened on several occasions.
I didn't know what to do about it.
Now, with all of this life that you were living,
tell us - what was the effect of this on your marriage and what was happening in your marital life?
I didn't see my wife as a woman.
I didn't have affection for her.
I always had my happiness when I was outside.
I enjoyed myself outside.
I came back late.
I lived the kind of life I wanted to live.
I had stopped eating my wife's food for months.
I would eat outside.
Whenever I was home, any time she wanted to ask me a question,
I would slap her. I would beat her.
I even told her, "Can't you read the handwriting on the wall?
Is it not better for you to pack your things and move out from this house?"
I have thrown my wife out of the house not less than three or four times.
Many pastors and family members came in to settle our problems
but nobody could settle the problem.
We have been together for more than 11 years
and we are looking for the fruit of the womb.
When she was pregnant, I went to the extent of beating her, misbehaving as I was always doing,
to the extent that she lost the pregnancy of six months.
She delivered the baby when it was not okay to deliver the baby - at six months.
Because you had beaten her up - it was the force that caused her to deliver?
Yes, when all these things came up, I would break things in my house -
the centre table, the television.
I would even use my standing fan to hit her.
I did a lot of things.
When I realised myself, I would feel pity for her.
But once that spirit came up, I wouldn't even see her like my wife.
I didn't even realise that she is a beautiful woman like this.
I was seeing these women outside as the best.
I felt happy when I was not in my home.
I always felt bad when I was coming home.
So, if I was coming home, what she just needed to do,
was to go and sleep in her own room because I had told her,
"I don't want to be sleeping with you. You have to stay in your own room
and I have to stay in my own room".
Once I was in, the best thing that happened to her, was that I went inside my room.
I would lock it because if I didn't lock it, she would come and start to hit at my door,
that I should open my room for her so that she would sleep with me.
I didn't want her to sleep with me because I had already been satisfied outside.
If I came back and she would be asking me questions, I would start beating her.
Now, brother, we just want to understand.
People who looked at you at the outside - did they ever know that
such thing was happening in your home or you were experiencing such terrible problems?
Everybody that knew me - I put on good clothes, I drive big cars -
they didn't know that I was dying inside.
I didn't have a solution.
I knew that something was seriously wrong.
I went to many churches but there was no solution to my problem.
Did it ever come to a point where you felt like giving up on life?
Not once.
I even told my wife many times - she is here, she is my live witness -
that I would put an end to this.
I thought of committing suicide many times.
Even one time when I was driving with her, I got annoyed and told her,
"You see we are on top of the bridge. Do you know that I can just drive this thing directly to that end?
Everybody will just die. All these problems will end because I am tired of all these problems".
She wouldn't even talk. It was even better for her not to utter a word
because if she would have said something good or bad, it would have worsened the situation.
I didn't like her to advise me or tell me what to do.
I didn't regard her words.
I thought about commmitting suicide many times.
I kept on wondering what I was going to do.
My beloved mother introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
I installed it in my room.
Any time I was home, I would put on the channel
but I kept on pretending to my mother because she always called me and asked me,
"I hope you are watching Emmanuel TV". I replied, "Yes".
But when I looked at it, everything looked fake to me.
I would just pretend and tell her, "Yes, I am watching it".
But I didn't believe - I just saw it as an arrangement.
I said to myself, "How can this be possible?"
It kept on going like that.
So you mean when watching Emmanuel TV, if you saw a deliverance and someone was demon-possessed -
what would you say, what was your reaction?
I always said that this was a planned something.
They might have arranged it with the person.
I didn't believe all these things because I was a Thomas, I didn't believe in anything.
I believed in seeing something before believing in it.
I kept on watching Emmanuel TV when I felt like it.
I saw what happened to other families.
Whenever I talked with my mother, she always continued telling me, "Keep on watching Emmanuel TV!
That what is happening to other people will surely happen to you".
Everybody knew that I had a big problem but they didn't know the solution to that.
I was a very angry person.
When I got angry, I could destroy things. I would break things.
I would even fight my younger brother with a bottle.
When I was angry like that, even my wife would run into her own room and lock it
because in my flat, I would break the doors - not less than ten times.
Ok, brother. Now we understood how severely these evil spirits affected your life.
You said your mother introduced you to Emmanuel TV and insisted
that you kept on watching and came down to The SCOAN.
What actually finally led you to be here at The SCOAN?
Because people would see me, "Ah, this man is a big man. He has big cars. He puts on good clothes"
but they didn't know what I was passing through.
So I began to give it a second thought.
I said to myself, "Let me go there".
When I was coming to The SCOAN, I was just coming here, I didn't believe.
I said to myself, "Let me come and see what is happening here".
The very first day I came, when the wise men were laying hands on people,
when they started coming towards my direction, I saw a different thing.
The fire was coming towards my direction.
I could not resist it.
When the man of God layed his hand on me, I fell down.
The ushers told me to stand here because he was coming back.
I managed to collect my Bible, ran and escaped from the church.
So the first day you came here, you actually ran out of the church?
Yes, I escaped because what I saw that day was a different thing - I could not withstand it.
I wanted to leave from here without my wife but she knew me very well.
Once I got angry, she knew that I would leave her.
She came after me and I did not even talk to her.
We drove for more than an hour and got home.
I then began to realise, "What is happening to me?"
My wife put the TV on - to the same place where we were coming from.
We were watching the same channel.
She would not utter any word because she knew very well
that if she said anything, I might even break her head.
I sat down and began to ponder, "What is going on in my life?"
After that, the next week I prepared and said, "I am going back to The SCOAN".
I came here again.
It happened that when the wise men started laying hands,
Wise Man Daniel came towards my direction, the same thing happened.
But, Children of God, I have to tell you something.
You might be coming here but the day must surely be your day.
That day, everything that is troubling you will come to an end.
Everybody has his own day.
That very day, that very blessed day, I tried to escape
but it was like all the ushers - everybody - prepared and were waiting for me.
Mr Okpalaeze Chidi - Deliverance Testimony
So they didn't give me any gap.
When Wise Man Daniel was praying for people, immediately he came towards my direction,
the fire - I couldn't even look at his eyes.
When he came directly to me, the fire was so much, I didn't know where I was again.
I found myself on the floor and woke up.
I knew that I was saying something but I couldn't control it.
I didn't know what was coming out from my mouth.
After my deliverance, my wife told me everything that happened.
When I woke up, I saw myself in the middle of the church.
You know, Children of God, it is here that I found out that God exists
because what happened to me that very day...
Mr Okpalaeze Chidi - Deliverance Testimony
...I had never experienced that before.
The fire was coming from every angle.
But when I just woke up on the ground, I realised myself.
I feel like a heavy block, bag of cement, moved out of my body.
I feel light.
I feel ashamed of myself - before I was not ashamed of anything.
I started to feel ashamed.
I feel very light.
I recognise my wife. I see her now as very beautiful.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Mr Okpalaeze Chidi - Deliverance Testimony
What are the changes you have immediately experienced after this experience?
Children of God, after my deliverance, I was singing with my wife when we were driving home.
We now eat together, pray together and sleep in the same room - not even the same room but the same bed.
Testimony Time
I keep on asking her to forgive me.
I looked at her hair and the following day I gave her money and said,
"This hairstyle is not good. She should go and get a different one".
Mr Okpalaeze Chidi - Deliverance Testimony
I sleep like a newborn baby.
I wake up soundly.
Before, if I wanted to sleep, I would go to my bar and drink like two glasses of a hot drink
or anything that was there to make me to sleep.
But this time around, I don't take any pills or alcohol.
I sleep like a baby. I wake up 100% fit.
I feel like jumping around.
I know that a lot of people out there are the same Thomas like I was.
I believed that seeing is believing.
You need to see and believe.
If the God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua can do this for me, He will do it for everybody.
Even for you Thomas that are out there.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
My business, what I ordered now - just one week after my deliverance -
the goods came in successfully and we did the promo.
The business is booming; it is going on now.
So, I have a lot of changes.
I have a good relationship with people,
I have a good relationship with my wife -
we discuss everything together what I want to do.
And you are no longer going outside to meet other women?
I don't even have the urge to go outside.
She would even be the one to tell me,
"Why can't you go out, drive around and come back?"
I would reply, "No, I am tired".
I don't have the urge to go around.
As from that day, I don't see alcohol as anything.
Women will see me...
On Valentine's Day, she told me, "We passed so many girls and nobody looked at you".
Before, she would have a problem with women, every time we would be out together.
A lot of changes.
Those things that I was experiencing then, I now no longer experience them.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
This is the deliverance that is happening here every day at The SCOAN
and I know many of us here today are ready and expecting to receive their own deliverance.
We know that as you receive your deliverance, you too will stands in the midst of God's people
to share your testimony.
So, finally, sir, what is your advice to viewers around the world and those present here?
Especially those who are sceptical, cynical about what is happening here
as you once were - what is your message to them?
First of all, I want to ask God to forgive me
and I want to ask our Daddy in the Lord, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua for forgiveness,
because I am one of those people that said one bad thing or the other against this place.
My advice to the whole world - the viewers and especially the Thomases like I once was:
You have to believe in God and try and come to The SCOAN for your deliverance.
You might be there, driving big cars, and the things that I experienced in my life are happening to you.
You need to come down here and have your deliverance
because everybody that is having this kind of problem needs deliverance.
Once you have been delivered, you will see a lot of changes.
You will see a difference in your life.
And I believe that that God that did it for me will also do it for everyone of you, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We thank God for your life, sir.
We just want to hear a quick word from your wife -
to hear from her, her own side of the testimony.
Madam, you are very welcome.
Just introduce yourself to us and tell us what you can say about your husband's wonderful deliverance.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Stella Okpalaeze.
The man beside me is my lovely husband.
He has already said everything.
But I also have things to say.
When this was going on, he hated me with passion.
He didn't even wanted to see me. Even though I cooked, he said the food was not good.
Anything I did in the house was not good.
He beat me the way he wanted to.
Sometimes I would be begging him: If I did anything wrong, he should please forgive me.
He replied, "You have not done anything to me but I don't want you see you".
He told me many times to leave the house but I refused to leave.
The family accused me, telling him that I was the cause of all this. He should drive me away.
We were still there.
Last January, when the thing was severe, each time I watched Emmanuel TV, I kept on praying.
I used to see many things happening here. Even broken homes were brought back together.
I knew it would happen for my husband and I.
Each time we were coming here, if the wise men touched him, he would run away.
I would not talk because if I talked, it would become a problem
so I would just keep quiet.
If he went out, I would be praying.
I would put Emmanuel TV on and pray, "God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua,
each time I am here, locate me and my husband".
If the problem is from me, let's go there.
If Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua sees us and the problem is from me,
I know the problem will be solved.
I didn't even tell him that the problem is from him; I kept on accepting it.
Even when men of God came to settle us when we were having problems
I would say that I was the problem.
I believed that one day things would be okay.
So, the first time we came here, they touched him and he started to manifest.
They told him to stay behind. He ran away.
I followed him immediately because I knew he would leave me here and go.
When I followed him and entered the car, I did not talk.
I phoned one of his friends and said, "Please, you are the only one that can help me!
Next Sunday we will come here again.
When we come, if they touch him, don't allow him to go.
Help me to hold him so that they will do the deliverance.
I know that when they will do his own, they will also do mine".
The friend accepted.
We came here together on the 26th of January.
When we came here, the same thing happened when they touched him.
He wanted to (leave). I looked at the friend and the friend said, "Don't worry".
The friend went to one of the ushers and told him, "Don't allow this man to go!"
He said, "Ok".
That is how they held him.
Testimony Time
Mr & Mrs Okpalaeze - Deliverance Testimony
That is how they held him.
They started the deliverance and I was also praying, "God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Help me! I'm in your house today! Help me! This problem is too much for me!"
That was how they did the deliverance; things went well.
I thank God today that everything is okay between my husband and I.
I believe that even the baby that I lost,
the God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua will still make me to have my own child, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Testimony Time
So, Madam, you mean that after your husband's deliverance, he is now a changed man?
He is now a changed man. He now loves me very much.
He tells me many things.
Even when I am cooking, he will say, "Let me come and help you". I will say, "No".
All the things he broke in the house, he brought them back under two days.
He gives me money. He takes care of me.
If I do like this, he will ask, "Are you okay?". I will say, "Yes".
Wow. Indeed the evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed.
What a wonderful testimony of reconciliation!
Madam, throughout this terrible ten-year turbulent period with your husband,
you never left him, you stayed with him
and today we give glory to God Almighty for your life.
What is your advice to other couples?
Especially to women who are in a similar situation you were in. What is your advice to them?
My advice to all women that are in this situation that I was in before
or maybe you have gone through this problem,
the only thing is God because then, friends - everybody - would tell me, "Leave him.
File a case and go to the law court".
They said that I should go here or there.
I replied, "I will not go anywhere. I don't even have money to give to anybody to do something for me.
It is only the God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua that will solve my problem".
The advice I am giving to you is to believe in God
because if you see yourself in that condition, people will be advising you to do this or that.
Don't run to anywhere.
Don't even go to any native doctor or any person because of your husband.
Keep on praying and believe that one day, God will do it.
The God that did it for me, that I am happy today, that God will do it for you, in Jesus' name!
Testimony Time
Mr & Mrs Okpalaeze - Deliverance Testimony
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.